Vijay Sanjay Nale

E-mail: vijaynale16111995@gmail.com Contact No: +91 8208078704

SUMMARY:

Data scientist with one year of experience in predictive modeling, data processing, and data mining algorithms to solve challenging business problems. Strong background in computer programming language, and knowledge of various types of machine learning, deep learning, and forecasting.

TECHNICAL SKILLS:

Programming Languages: C++, Python

Database: SQL , MongoDB **Knowledge In Technology:**

- Data Analysis with Python.
- Data Visualization with Python and Tableau.
- Machine Learning with Python (Linear Regression, Logistic Regression, KNN, k-Means Clustering, PCA, Decision Tree, Random Forest, SVM, Recommender Systems)
- Deep learning, Artificial Intelligence, Neural Network, CNN, RNN, Tensorflow object detection
- Deployment of model (Flask, Heroku)
- Knowledge in HTML, CSS, Javascript.
- Ms Excel, Ms word.

WORKING EXPERIENCE:

AD OPERATIONS ANALYST

10/2019 - 09/2020

Accel Digital Ad Operations

- Determine success metrics and report on the effectiveness of campaigns while overseeing the day to day operations.
- Report and Analysis: Pull daily or weekly reports to analyze campaign performance, Use SQL queries / Tableau / DCM to fetch reports, build and run custom reports in DCM.
- Communication with account managers as chats on reporting,
- Providing training and mentoring to new joiners in the team.

INTERNSHIP:

A) Data Science Intern

03/2019 - 09/2019

Innodatatics

- Requirement discussions with the team and understand the manual workaround done by the team.
- Review the estimates for work items, help one another with impact analysis and participate in estimation justification meetings with the team.
- Involved in Data Pre-processing Techniques such as data cleaning, visualizing the data, identifying outliers and making data ready for Machine Learning Techniques.
- Machine Learning Algorithms Evaluation.
- Analyze the results of all algorithm outcomes and deciding the best one
- Model Deployment process once signoff is in place.

B) Data Scientist Intern

iNeuron.ai

08/2020 - PRESENT

- Requirement discussions with the team and understand the manual workaround done by the
- Images collection from various sites by use of web scraping or manual collection of images.
- Perform data preparation by image standardization size each and data augmentation for increasing the training size and model generalization
- Review the estimates for work items, help one another with impact analysis and participate in estimation justification meetings with the team.
- To make data ready for Deep learning object detection Techniques, and Algorithms Evaluation.
- Analyze the results of all algorithm outcomes and deciding the best one.

Project 1: Warehouse retail domain

Team size 6

Role: Intern Data scientist

We are building an automated solution of detecting missing boxes in a warehouse by leveraging Deep Learning. We aim to build a pallet and box detection technique using object detection and tracking that can be deployed and served for continuous prediction in real time.

(Python, TensorFlow, object detections, Faster RCNN, SSD)

Github: https://github.com/VijayNale/Warehouse

Project 2: Incident Raised by the customer.

Team size 4

Role: Intern Data scientist

In this project, The dataset is having incidents raised by customers. Which contains an event log of an incident management process extracted from a service desk platform of an IT company.

(Python, K-Nearest Neighbors, Random Forest, Extreme Gradient Boosting)

Github: https://github.com/VijayNale/incident_project

EDUCATION:

Master of Computer Application(<u>C.B.S.E Board</u>), June 2019 Shivaji University, Kolhapur.

Bachelor of Science(Computer Science), June 2016

Gopal Krishna Gokhale College, Kolhapur.

CERTIFICATIONS:

- Data Science Master Certification from ExcelR solution.
- **Internet of Things** conducted workshop attend in Shivaji university for one week.
- Machine learning Master Certification from iNeuron.ai

EXTRA CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Inter-college cricket tournament participation

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date of Birth : 16th November 1995
Languages Known : English , Hindi , Marathi
Github Profile : https://github.com/VijayNale

■ LikedIn Profile : https://www.linkedin.com/in/vijay-nale-45196a1